A Finding Aid to the Colin de Land Collection, 1968-2008, bulk 1980-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.delacoli
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Material, bulk 1980-2003; 1968-2003; Series 1; 12 Linear feet Box 1-12
  - Snapshots, bulk 1980-2003; 1968-2003; 1.1
    - American Fine Arts and Cape Cod, circa 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Includes photos of Jacqueline Humphries and Spencer Sweeney; Takahiro Imamura and Daniel McDonald with taxidermied bear; Pat Hearn in Cape Cod, [Marion Hearn?], Colin de Land.
    - American Fine Arts, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      Includes photos of Daniel McDonald, Takahiro Imamura, John Armleder, Pat Hearn, Christine Tsvetanov and J. Morgan Puett, Peter Fend. Negatives also include some Global Warming performance photographs.
    - London, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Merlin Carpenter, and Mark Dion.
    - Openings at Team Gallery and American Fine Arts, 1999 January (Box 8, Folder 16)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Peter Fend, Christine Tsvetanov, Takahiro Imamura, Shannon Pultz, Jess Holzworth, Jan Avgikos, Cris Moor, Daniel McDonald, Spencer Sweeney, Nils Norman, Jennifer Bolande, Actress collective; Tam Ochiai and Steven Parrino event at Team Gallery; opening of Dennis Balk exhibition Photo-Magnetic Receiver (1999) at American Fine Arts; Marden box.
    - Takahiro Imamura and Daniel McDonald, 1999 January (Box 8, Folder 17)
      Includes photos of Takahiro Imamura, Daniel McDonald; Balk installation; Toad Hall Bar and Café.
    - Taka/Fend, 1999 January; Includes negatives only. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Holzworth's Arctic Expedition, 1999 January; Includes negatives only. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Colin de Land and Dennis Balk, 1999 January 23 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      Includes portraits of Colin de Land and Dennis Balk, with Daniel McDonald, [Daniela Salvioni?] and Peter Fend.
    - American Fine Arts, 1999 January-February (Box 8, Folder 21)
      Includes photos of Takahiro Imamura, Peter Fend and Daniel McDonald with Marden cow box, Steven Shearer, Liz-and-Val, pills.
    - American Fine Arts, Dan Graham, 1999 January-February (Box 8, Folder 22)
      Includes photos of Paul Morris, Sam Grubman, Pat Hearn, members of the Hearn Family, Tom Jarmusch, Daniel McDonald, Takahiro Imamura, Lizzi Bougatsos, Jess Holzworth, Actress collective, Marden cow box, Dennis Balk installation, Dan Graham studio.
    - Brooklyn, Hotel, Television Shots, 1999 February (Box 8, Folder 23)
      Includes photos of South Brooklyn Casket Co., Blake Rayne with Botero sculpture in hotel lobby, and rephotographed television screens.
    - Armory Show, From Matthew Marks, 1999 February (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Includes photos of the Armory Show with a note from Matthew Marks Gallery.
    - Armory Show, 1999 February (Box 8, Folder 25)
      Includes photographs of first Armory Show in 69th Regiment Armory, Rudiger Schottle, Jorg Johnen, Seth Shapiro fashion show, Takahiro Imamura with Dennis Balk magnifying glass, Daily Soup restaurant, David Karlin, Peter Fend, Georg Kargl, Daniel McDonald, Lizzi Bougatsos, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, and Christine Tsvetanov.
    - Marriage License, 1999 March (Box 8, Folder 26)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land and Pat Hearn applying for their marriage license; Paul Morris, Sam Grubman at the Four Seasons; Marc Latamie with Duchamp box, Jess Holzworth, Almine Rech, Bernard Picasso, Peter Fend, Daniel McDonald, Takahiro Imamura, Spencer Sweeney.
    - De Land Hearn Wedding, MoMA Opening, 1999 March (Box 8, Folder 27)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land and Pat Hearn’s wedding at New York’s City Hall. Guests included Sam Grubman, Nan Goldin, Nils Norman, Jackie McAllister, Peter Fend, Mary Heilmann, David Karlin, Daniel McDonald, Daniel Reich, Matthew Marks, Sophie Calle, Dennis Balk, John Hearn, Craig Wadlin, Brice Marden, Torsten Wiesel, Jean Stein, [Joan Jonas?], [Jane Beckwith?]. Also includes photos of the opening reception for Museum as Muse (1999) at MoMA, New York, with photos of Andrea Fraser, Hans Haacke, Takahiro Imamura, Colin de Land, Mark Dion, Nils Norman, and Daniel McDonald, plus Rikrit Tiravanija and Elizabeth Peyton at American Fine Arts.
    - Various Subjects, 1999 March-April (Box 8, Folder 28)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn at St. Vincent’s Hospital, with Mary Heilmann. Jack Pierson, Colin de Land, Takahiro Imamura, Nils Norman, Daniel McDonald, Jacqueline Humphries, Peter Fend, Christine Tsvetanov, Frank Schroder, and Cosima von Bonin. Also includes Roy Arden show at Tom Cugliani Gallery.
    - Martinique Honeymoon, 1999 April (Box 8, Folder 29)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Paul Morris, and Sam Grubman.
    - Anita Pallenberg Set, Martinique, American Fine Arts, 1999 April (Box 8, Folder 30)
      Includes on-set photos during the filming of The Anita Pallenberg Story by Laura Cottingham and Leslie Singer, with Colin de Land, Cosima von Bonin, Clarissa Dalrymple, Nicole Eisenman, Gavin Brown, Rainer Ganahl, Aaron Corbett, and Laura Cottingham. Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Sam Grubman, Paul Morris in Martinique. At American Fine Arts, photos include Ed Schott and his mother, Rosalie Knox, Jess Holzworth, Daniel McDonald, Takahiro Imamura, and Lizzi Bougatsos.
    - Waters and Stein Dinner, Frankfurt Art Fair, 1999 April (Box 8, Folder 31)
      Includes photos of dinner with Pat Hearn, John Waters, Torsten Wiesel, and Jean Stein; brown water at 440 West 24th Street; Takahiro Imamura; newspapers; gift from Elizabeth Peyton. Also includes photographs from the Frankfurt Art Fair, including of Esther Friedman, the joint American Fine Arts/Friedman/Guinness booth, artwork by Mark Dion, Peter Fend, Garry Gross, John Waters, Jack Pierson.
    - American Fine Arts and Frankfurt Art Fair, 1999 April 20-30 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      Includes photos of Takahiro Imamura, Daniel McDonald, Esther Friedman, a protest in Frankfurt, a roll of Renee Greene designed wallpaper, wedding gifts for Pat de Land and Colin Hearn from Gillian, Garry Gross with photograph of Brooke Shields and artwork by Jack Pierson.
    - American Fine Arts, Spring 1999 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Nils Norman, Robert Lederman, with paintings by Robert Lederman and 1999 installation by Art Club 2000, Takahiro Imamura, Spencer Sweeney, medical documents and equipment. Includes additional negatives with no prints.
    - Bee-In, May 1999 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Takahiro Imamura, Patterson Beckwith, Charlie Finch, Lizzi Bougatsos, Jane Beckwith, Antek Walczak, [Ally Pultz?], [Colette?], Jess Holzworth.
    - Colin de Land's Family, Pierson Show, 1999 May 18 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      Includes photos of a family dinner, with Colin de Land, Aleta Hamada, Dr. Hamada, Colin de Land’s aunt. Also includes photos of April 1998 Jack Pierson show by Red Ed with Katkitty.
    - Red Ed, Blanche, Art Club 2000, 1999 June (Box 8, Folder 36)
      Includes photos of Carol Braddock (Red Ed), Massimo Audiello, Blanche (Chihuahua puppy), John Saaci, Pat Hearn, Colin de Land. Also includes artwork by Robert Smithson and Art Club 2000, with Christine Tsvetanov and Todd Parkin.
    - American Fine Arts, 1999 June-July (Box 8, Folder 37)
      Includes photographs of Colin de Land, Rachel Harrison, Reverend Jen Miller, Christine Tsvetanov, Peter Fend, Jess Holzworth, Lizzie Bougatsos, and Daniel McDonald; Casey Kaplan Gallery; artwork by Dan Graham, Jan Dibbets, Christo, and Mark Dion.
    - Fourth of July at the Marden Home, 1999 July 4 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      With photographs of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Brice Marden, Helen Marden, Matthew Marks, Jack Bankowsky, invitation to 1972 Brice Marden exhibition at Bykert Gallery; rephotographed photos of Brice Marden, Fran Lebowitz, and others.
    - Cape Cod, 1999 August (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
      Includes photographs of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Christian Philipp Muller, Carol Greene, [Markus?], Morris Simon, [Marion Hearn?], Jack Pierson, Tom Borgese, Maureen Gallace, JFK Museum, Hyannis, Against the Grain Gallery. Also includes laminated photo of Pat Hearn in front of Puritan Clothing Co.
    - Jack Pierson Birthday, Pat Hearn Art Gallery, 1999 September-October (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Includes photos of Paul Morris, Pat Hearn, and Sam Grubman at Harry Cipriani; Daniel McDonald, Jess Holzworth, Takahiro Imamura, Peter Fend, Mio Shirai and husband, Norman Rosenthal with Sensation exhibition Newsday cover story at AFA; birthday dinner for Jack Pierson with Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, John Derian, Tom Borgese; Pat Hearn and Daniel Reich at Pat Hearn Art Gallery.
    - Sensation Exhibition, Brooklyn Museum, Fall 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Includes photos of protests outside of the Brooklyn Museum during the exhibition Sensation (1999-2000); Colin de Land, Paul Morris, and Sam Grubman on a country outing; John Armleder.
    - London, circa October 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Includes photos of Mark Dion, J. Morgan Puett, Spencer Sweeney, Hillary Smalls, Merlin Carpenter, and London street scenes.
    - London, AFA Truck, circa October 1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land and Merlin Carpenter in London. Also includes photos of the American Fine Arts pickup truck being towed, as well as photos of Stephen Shearer, Daniel McDonald, Takahiro Imamura, and Spencer Sweeney.
    - American Fine Arts, 1999 October-November (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Includes photos of Aki Fujiyoshi, Michael Clegg, Roddy Bogawa, Mark Dion, J. Morgan Puett, Moyra Davey, Daniel McDonald, Pat Hearn, Takahiro Imamura, Christine Tsvetanov, Jess Holzworth, Rosalie Knox, Rachel Harrison, artwork by Steven Shearer, Mark Dion and Nils Norman (Hiriya Portfolio) and Moyra Davey.
    - Massimo Audiello Birthday, 1999 October (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Includes photos of Massimo Audiello, Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, Blanche, and others.
    - Mark Dion at the Carnegie Museum of Art, 1999 November (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Includes photos of Mark Dion installations Ornithological Selections from the Collections of Carnegie Museum of Art and Alexander Wilson—Studio at the Carnegie Museum of Art as part of the Carnegie International.
    - Schoolwerth Studio, Michelle Tsvetanov, 1999 November (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Includes photos of Pieter Schoolwerth’s studio; Michelle Tsvetanov at American Fine Arts, with artwork by Stephen Shearer.
    - Dope: An XXX-Mas Show, 1999 December (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Massimo Audiello, Takahiro Imamura, Rosalie Knox, [Chloe Sevigny?], John Waters, Sylvia Kolbowski, Daniel McDonald, Ed Schott, Patterson Beckwith, Craig Wadlin, Glyniss McDaris, Lizzi Bougatsos, Hillary Smalls, David Karlin, Rachel Harrison, Daniel Reich, Melia Marden. Also includes photocopy of Colin de Land portrait.
    - Christmas, 1999 December (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Massimo Audiello, John Waters, Paul Morris, Sam Grubman, Carol Greene, [Markus?], Jacqueline Humphries. Also includes photos of a gallery installation with a video viewing room.
    - Car Cover, Pub, 1999 December-2000 April (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Includes photos of Hillary Smalls and Matt McAuly with portrait by Alex Bag, Peter Fend, Takahiro Imamura, Rapid Response: Post Petroleum Gas Station with Peter Fend, [Christina Cobb, Julia Fischer and William Meyer?], Daniel McDonald, Mark Dion, Emma Chapa, Liz-and-Val, Dan Graham, David Karlin, and [Paul?]. Also includes photo of pick up truck with covered bed.
    - Beach, circa 2000 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Includes photographs of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Paul Morris, Sam Grubman, Brice Marden, and Helen Marden.
    - American Fine Arts at Pat Hearn Art Gallery Party, circa 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Includes photos of party with band and costumes held at Pat Hearn Art Gallery with Patterson Beckwith, John Waters, Takahiro Imamura, Pieter Schoolwerth, Spencer Sweeney, Emma Chapa, Jutta Koether, Niki Gerakos, Alex Bag, Lily Ludlow, Chloe Sevigny, Peter Fend, and Merlin Carpenter.
    - London, circa 2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Merlin Carpenter, Emily Pethick, Nils Norman, photograph of poster for the People’s Flag Show at Judson Memorial Church, concert, Takahiro Imamura.
    - Pay While You Wait and Marden Home, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Includes photos taken at American Fine Arts during the Team404 and John Armleder collective project “Play While You Wait”, with photos of Patterson Beckwith, Takahiro Imamura, and Liz-and-Val. Also includes photos of a trip to Brice Marden’s home Rainbow Farms, Eagles Mere, Pennsylvania, with Paul Morris, Sam Grubman, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Brice Marden, and Helen Marden.
    - Marden Home, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Includes photos taken at the home of Brice Marden in Eagles Mere, PA, with Matthew Marks, Fran Lebowitz, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Helen Marden, Mirabelle Marden, Melia Marden, and Brice Marden.
    - Various Subjects, 2000 March (Box 9, Folder 20)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Karen Hallock, Spencer Sweeney and Rachel Harrison possibly at the home of a collector, Daniel McDonald, Christian Philipp Muller, Cris Moor, Takahiro Imamura, artwork by Mark Dion.
    - Global Warming Performance, Schoolwerth Exhibition, 2000 April (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Includes photos of the Peter Fend and Rapid Response Global Warming performance and installation shots of Pieter Schoolwerth exhibition The Black Rainbow Domino's Effect on the Infinite Burgundy Line (2000) at AFA.
    - Global Warming Performance, 2000 April 25 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      Includes photos of Peter Fend and two others at AFA with Global Warming sign for Rapid Response performance. Also includes photo of Pieter Schoolwerth painting.
    - Schoolwerth Paintings, 2000 April 25 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      Includes photos of Pieter Schoolwerth exhibition The Black Rainbow Domino's Effect on the Infinite Burgundy Line (2000) at American Fine Arts, with Pieter Schoolwerth. Also includes photos of a beach.
    - Christian Philipp Muller, Marden Home, 2000 May (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Includes photos of a Christian Philipp Muller installation in progress at AFA, with Christian Philipp Muller, Daniel McDonald, Frank Schroder, Colin de Land, and Takahiro Imamura. Includes elements of Rapid Response: Post Petroleum Gas Station, with unidentified family portrait [possibly with Christina Cobb or Julia Fischer?]. Also includes photos taken at the Marden home, with Helen Marden, Matthew Marks, Colin de Land, Mirabelle Marden, Melia Marden, as well as television screens with Cher.
    - Various Subjects, Summer 2000 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Rachel Harrison, Jacqueline Humphries, Patterson Beckwith, police officers, artwork by Kiki Smith.
    - Home of Jean Stein, 2000 June or July (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Jean Stein, and Massimo Audiello.
    - American Fine Arts and Printed Matter, circa July 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      Includes photos of Jess Holzworth, Spencer Sweeney, John Waters, Lizzi Bougatsos, Hillary Smalls, Matt McAuley, Colin de Land, Daniel McDonald. Also includes photos of Wooster Street, artwork by John Waters, and a pigeon labeled Pecker. Some photos taken at AFA and some at Printed Matter.
    - Bee-In, circa August 2000 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Includes photos of Jane Beckwith’s Bee In at AFA, Wooster Street, Lizzi Bougatsos, Daniel McDonald, Spencer Sweeney, Takahiro Imamura.
    - Cape Cod and Various, 2000 August (Box 9, Folder 29)
      Includes photos of Alice Hearn, William Hearn, [Marion Hearn?], and other members of the Hearn family with Pat Hearn shortly before her death, Daniel Reich, Colin de Land, [Simon Leung?], Bruce Fuller. Also includes photos of Julian Schnabel taken in Venice and photos of Takahiro Imamura, Colin de Land, Jacqueline Humphries at American Fine Arts. Included in envelope are also one late photograph of Colin de Land and Kembra Pfahler and two prints of Colin de Land (after a portrait of Jean-Luc Godard by F.C. Gundlach) by Greg Gorman.
    - Cape Cod, 2000 August (Box 9, Folder 30)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn and a parade in Provincetown, MA.
    - Pat Hearn Death, Cape Cod, 1993; 2000 August (Box 9, Folder 31)
      Includes photos of death of Pat Hearn, memorial party at the home of Pat de Groot, Provincetown, Massachusetts, Jackie McAllister, Carol Greene, Jacqueline Humphries, [Markus], Spencer Sweeney, Alex Bag, Daniel McDonald, [Pieter Schoolwerth?], Lisa Spellman, Patterson Beckwith, Pat de Groot, John Waters, Dennis Balk, Paul Morris, Jim Toth, Josephine Pryde, Stephan Dillemuth, Peter Fend, and Renee Green. The envelope also included two photos of 1993 Gramercy International Contemporary Art Fair.
    - Miniature Golf, 2000 August (Box 9, Folder 32)
      Includes photos of a game of miniature golf in Cape Cod, with Colin de Land, Patterson Beckwith, Rene Green, Jess Holzworth, Spencer Sweeney, Josephine Pryde, Stephen Dillemuth, Dennis Balk, and Daniel McDonald.
    - Pat Hearn Memorial, Providence, Rhode Island, 2000 August (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Includes photos of Kerry Armington, Marjie Sheehan, Miranda Hearn, John Hearn, William Hearn, Spencer Sweeney, Eileen Herbert, Louise Dunn, Sam Grubman, Elliott Hearn, Colin de Land, Alice Hearn, Amanda Hearn, Marion Hearn, Rene Green, Peter Fend, Marie Hearn, Mena McLaughlin, Paul Morris, Winnie Lawless, Frank Darcy, Paddy McLaughlin, Chandler Hearn, rephotographed Hearn family photos.
    - Pat Hearn Memorial Sevice, St. Marks-on-the-Bowery Church, 2000 August (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Pat Hearn Memorial Dinner, Matthew Marks Gallery, Fall 2000 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn memorial dinner at Matthew Marks Gallery, with Colin de Land, members of the Hearn family, Matthew Marks, Takahiro Imamura. Also includes photos at American Fine Arts of Colin de Land, Margaret Deluccia, and Jess Holzworth, and artwork: animal sculptures and a framed picture marked To Jack Pierson.
    - Pat Hearn Memorial Dinner and Pat Hearn Art Gallery, Fall 2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn memorial dinner at Matthew Marks Gallery and gathering at Pat Hearn Art Gallery, with Colin de Land, Alice Hearn, John Hearn, Jack Pierson, Tom Burr, Daniel McDonald, Daniel Reich, Pat de Groot, Massimo Audiello, Margaret Deluccia, Spencer Sweeney, Carol Greene, Emma Chapa, David Karlin, Takahiro Imamura, Rachel Harrison, Leslie Nolen, Patterson Beckwith, Chivas Clem, Chandler Hearn, and Sam Grubman.
    - Cape Cod, 2000 September (Box 10, Folder 5-7)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land driving with picture of Pat Hearn on his dashboard, Carol Greene, [Markus?], Patterson Beckwith, Jess Holzworth, Barbara Morse, Howard Morse, Jack Pierson, Tom Borgese, Pat de Groot, Jack and Rachel Tworvok’s grave, and shrine to Pat Hearn.
    - Germany, 2000 September-October (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Includes photos of Art Forum Berlin art fair, Christian Nagel, and Tom Burr exhibition Low Slung (2000) at Kunstverein Braunschweig.
    - Tom Burr Exhibition, Braunschweig, 2000 September-October (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Includes photos of the Tom Burr exhibition Low Slung (2000) at Kunstverein Braunschweig.
    - Art Forum Berlin, 2000 September-October (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Carol Greene, Christian Nagel, F.C. Gundlach.
    - Art Forum Berlin and Cape Cod, 2000 September-October (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, F.C. Gundlach, Carol Greene, Rachel Harrison, Christian Nagel, with artwork by J. Saint Bernard at Paris Bar. Also included are photos of Cape Cod street scenes.
    - Paris Party, 2000 October (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Includes photos of an opulent party, with Colin de Land, Tom Burr, Almine Rech, Bernard Picasso, Lawrence Weiner. Also includes Paris street scenes.
    - Paris Street Scenes, 2000 October (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
      Includes photos of Antek Walczak and Paris street scenes.
    - Paris Night Out, 2000 October (Box 10, Folder 15-17)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Antek Walczak, Frank Schroder and family, [Maripol?], unidentified band.
    - Paris and Various, 1970s; 2000 October (Box 10, Folder 18)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Maripol, Antek Walczak, and artwork by Maripol. Also includes early photos of Pat Hearn, including one at Madonna concert and one likely taken in the 1970s, Mary Heilmann and an unidentified woman, as well as Lizzi Bougatsos at American Fine Arts and Spencer Sweeney.
    - American Fine Arts, 2000 October (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Includes photos of AFA during Chris Verene exhibition, Colin de Land, Margaret Deluccia, artwork by Mark Morrisroe, thank you gift from Nikolai Fine Art, Pat Hearn t-shirt, broken window at American Fine Arts.
    - Night Out, 2000 November (Box 10, Folder 20)
      Includes photos of a party or night at a bar, with Colin de Land, Lizzi Bougatsos, Jess Holzworth, David Karlin, Red Ed, Paul Morris, Sam Grubman, Frank Schroder, Pieter Schoolwerth, Patterson Beckwith, Karen Hallock, and Christine Tsvetanov.
    - Colin de Land and Kembra Pfahler, circa 2001 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Colin de Land and Kembra Pfahler Road Trip, circa 2001 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Beach, circa 2001 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land and Kembra Pfahler at the beach.
    - California, circa 2001 (Box 10, Folder 24-26)
      Includes photos of Kembra Pfahler at the beach.
    - Colin de Land and Kembra Pfahler, circa 2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - The Voluptuous Horror of Karen Black and the Toilet Boys, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 2-5)
      Includes photos of The Voluptuous Horror of Karen Black, a Toilet Boys concert, Colin de Land, Daniel McDonald, Patterson Beckwith, John Waters, Jacqueline Humphries at Squeezebox. Also included are photos at AFA with Charlie Finch, John Waters, Jackie McAllister, Daniel McDonald, Grey Rabbit Dion-Puett, Mark Dion, Liz-and-Val, Rosalie Knox, Colin de Land, Red Ed, Carol Greene or Rhea Anastas, Patterson Beckwith, Dan Graham, Merlin Carpenter, Ed Schott. This is possibly during the November 2001 Spencer Sweeney exhibition. Also included are Lizzi Bougatsos at the Pat Hearn Gallery, and possible archeological dig by Mark Dion.
    - Bee-In, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
      Includes photos of a Bee-In event at AFA with Colin de Land, Kembra Pfahler, Daniel McDonald, Rosalie Knox, Patterson Beckwith, Ed Schott, Takahiro Imamura, Jane Beckwith, and David Karlin. Folder 7 also includes photos of Colin de Land and Kembra Pfahler at Pfahler's home.
    - American Fine Arts, 2001 March-April (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Includes photos mostly taken in AFA of Colin de Land, Takahiro Imamura, Patterson Beckwith, Karen Hallock, Daniel McDonald, Stephen Shearer, Liz-and-Val, Frank Schroder, Dan Asher, and altered photograph of Daniel McDonald and Colin de Land with ping pong ball eyes, in the style of Alex Bag project Crack Up.
    - Nils Norman Exhibition, Kembra Pfahler, 2001 May (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Includes photos of Nils Norman exhibition Geocruiser. The Mother Coach. Zone: Earth (2001) at American Fine Arts; Colin de Land and Kembra Pfahler at the home of Kembra Pfahler with Charles Addams cartoons.
    - Vienna, 2001 May-June (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Includes photos of Mary Heilmann show at Galerie Meyer Kainer, Vienna street scenes, television screens, VHS boxes, and photos of Mary Heilmann.
    - Nils Norman Exhibition and Venice Biennale, 2001 May-June (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Includes photos of Nils Norman exhibition at American Fine Arts and Colin de Land, Frank Schroder, and Orlan en route to Venice.
    - Venice Biennale, 2001 June (Box 11, Folder 12-18)